Hermann Hagedorn Papers
Hermann Hagedorn Papers
- Writings
  - Miscellaneous writings
    - Unidentified fragment of a play, undated; pp. 19-41, anno. ts (Box 4)
Eklund, Abel 1944 Nov 2 Needles, Calif. (ALS, to Walter G. Muelder)
Elliott, Errol T. 1946 Apr 5 Richmond, Ind. (ALS)
Ewing, Joseph M. 1946 Mar 15 Santa Barbara, Calif. (TLS)
Ficke, Arthur Davison 1936 Aug 16 Hillsdale, N.Y. (TLS)
Field, Marshall 1946 Mar 14 Chicago (TLS)
Field, Pearl Hendrick 1946 Jun 4 Beverly Hills, Calif. (ALS)
Fifield, James W. Jr. 1946 Apr 8 Los Angeles (ALS)
Fillmore, J.E. 1946 May 23 Leonia, N.J. (ALS)
Fillmore, Ina W. 1946 May 26 Leonia, N.J. (ALS)
Fisher, Dorothy Canfield 1946 Mar 16 Arlington, Vt. (TLS) 1946 Mar 28 Arlington, Vt. (ALS) 1946 Apr 2 Arlington, Vt. (TLS) 1946 Apr 16 Arlington, Vt. (TLS) 1946 Aug 23 Arlington, Vt. (TLS)
Ford, John Anson 1946 Jun 5 Los Angeles (TLS)
Fosdick, Harry Emerson 1946 Apr 8 New York (secretarial)
Francke, Kuno 1905 Aug? 16 Cambridge (ALS) 1905 Nov 11 Cambridge (ALS)
The Friend 1946 Apr 4 Philadelphia (secretarial)
Fritchman, Stephen H. 1946 Mar 23 Boston (TLS)
Gannon, Robert I. 1946 Mar 27 New York (TLS)
Garrison, Winfred Ernest 1946 Apr 15 Chicago (TLS, to Frank G. Tyrrell)
Goddard, Kathleen 1945 Jan 15 Santa Barbara, Calif. (TLS)
Goodrich, Arthur 1936 Mar 7 [New York] (ALS) 1936 Mar 12 n.p. (ALS) 1936 Mar 15 n.p. (ALS)
Goodwin, Maud Wilder no year Mar 10 Washington, D.C. (ALS) no year Aug 24 Seal Harbor (ALS) no year Oct 4 [New York] (ALS) no year Dec 25 Washington Court (ALS) 1905 Jul 19 Fieldwood Palace (ALS, to "Your Excellency" [H.H.Jr])
Goodykoontz, Susan Blakey 1946 Mar 28 Boulder, Col. (ANS)
Gras, N.S.B. 1947 Oct 22 Boston (TLS)
Green, Erastus H. 1946 May 15 W. Somerville, Mass. (TLS)
Green, William 1946 Apr 2 Washington (TLS)
Grew, Joseph C. 1946 Apr 22 Washington (TLS)
Guild, Curtis Jr. 1907 Jun 2 Boston (ALS)
Hagedorn, Hermann (All letters are represented by carbons, unless otherwise stated.) 1936 Mar 10 (to James Truslow Adams) no date (draft, to Bahn & Taylor) 1944 Oct 13 (to Kurt Bergel) 1944 Nov 15 1944 Dec 14 (to Julius Seelye Bixler) 1947 Sep 10 (to W.R. Boyd, Jr.) 1936 Feb 28 (to Van Wyck Brooks) 1936 Mar 10 1936 Mar 26 1945 Jun 28 (to C.E. Cahn-Bronner) 1936 Feb 28 (to Walter Damrosch) 1944 Oct 13 (2 copies, to Archibald Davison) 1944 Sep 15 (to Alice Ehlers) 1944 Oct 26 1944 Nov 21 1945 May 21 1947 Apr 16 (to [Abel] Eklund) 1936 Mar 10 (to Hamlin Garland) 1945 Jan 24 (to Kathleen Goddard) 1936 Feb 28 (to Arthur Goodrich) 1936 Mar 10 1945 Jun 28 (to W.K. Gottstein) 1947 Oct 23 (to N.S.B. Gras) 1945 Apr 9 (to Henry Holt & Company) 1947 Feb 28 1947 Apr 12 1944 Oct 13 (to T.E. Hume) 1944 Sep 15 (to Allen Hunter) 1944 Nov 14 (to Paul Hutchinson) no year Oct 10 (draft, to [Thomas W.] Lamont) 1947 Feb 28 (to Harold S. Latham) 1945 May 8 (to Edith G.H. Lenel) 1945 May 22 1945 May 28 1945 Jun 1 1945 Jun 4 1945 Jun 13 1945 Jun 19 1945 Jul 3 1945 Sep 7 1945 Nov 15 1936 Feb 28 (to Jonas Lie) 1945 Nov 15 (to Emmy Martin) 1947 Sep 13 (to Herryman Maurer) 1956 Mar 25 (to [ ] Meiner) 1945 May 21 (to Jeanne Mettenet) 1944 Sep 15 (to Missionary Education Movement) 1944 Oct 26 (to Charles Clayton Morrison) 1944 Oct 17 (to Walter G. Muelder) 1945 Jan 30 1945 Jul 6 1945 Feb 28 (2 copies, to Edouard Nies-Berger) 1945 Mar 26 1944 Dec 13 (to Hubert W. Peet) 1945 Feb 22 1945 Apr 30 1936 Mar 10 (to John Russell Pope) 1936 Mar 10 (to A. Phimister Proctor) 1944 Oct 13 (to John D. Regester) 1944 Oct 26 1944 Dec 13 (to Karl Reiland) 1945 Jan 15 1945 Jan 30 1944 Nov 14 (to A.A. Roback) 1945 Jun 22 1936 Mar 10 (to Elihu Root) 1936 Mar 10 (to F. Wellington Ruckstull) 1936 Mar 10 (to Ernest Schelling) 1944 Oct (to Albert Schweitzer) 1944 Oct 7 1944 Oct 18 1944 Oct 20 1944 Dec 13 1945 Jan 13 1945 Mar 14 1945 May 8 1945 May 10 1945 Jun 4 1945 Jul 9 1944 Oct 7 (to Hélène Schweitzer) 1945 Jul 21 1947 Feb 15 1947 Feb 28 (to Simon and Schuster, Inc., publishers) 1944 Oct 9 (to Everett Skillings 1944 Oct 20 1944 Nov 8 1944 Dec 13 1945 Jan 15 1945 Feb 13 1945 Jun 4 1945 Jun 28 1936 Mar 18 (to David H. Stevens 1944 Oct 13 (to Paul Tillich 1944 Nov 14 1945 Feb 13 (to Wilbur K. Thomas 1936 Mar 18 (to Mrs. William Vanamee 1936 Mar 10 (to Bessie Potter Vonnoh ?1940 Mar 8 (draft, to Henry C. Wallace 1944 Sep 15 (3 copies, to Richard J. Walsh 1944 Nov 21 (to Gisela Westhoff 1945 Feb 28 1947 Sep 10 (to Robert R. Young
Hagedorn, Ivan H. 1946 Mar 29 Philadelphia (TLS)
Hagedorn, John Joseph 1946 --- -- St. Louis, Mo. (TLS)
Halliday, Mary 1946 May 4 Santa Barbara, Calif. (ALS)
Hamlin, Chauncey J. 1946 Mar 22 Buffalo, N.Y. (ALS)
Hammond, Emily V. 1946 Apr 4 New York (ALS) 1946 Apr 8 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 30 New York (TLS) 1946 May 6 Mount Kisco, N.Y. (ALS)
Hapgood, Norman no year Mar 27 n.p. (ALS) no year Mar 30 n.p. (ALS) 1906 Jan 4 New York (TLS) 1907 Mar 25 New York (TLS)
Harcourt, Alfred 1946 May 7 Riverside, Ct. (ALS) 1946 May 26 Riverside, Ct. (ALS) 1946 Jun 6 Riverside, Ct. (ALS)
Hard, William 1945 Nov 25 Pleasantville, N.Y. (TLS) 1946 Apr 13 Pleasantville, N.Y. (TLS)
Hassler, Alfred 1946 Jul 3 New York (TLS) 1946 Jul 9 New York (secretarial)
Hays, Will H. 1946 Mar 16 Camarillo, Calif. (TLS) 1946 Apr 18 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 30 New York (TLS)
Hellman, George S. 1936 Jul 2 New York (ALS)
Hitchcock, Helen 1946 Apr 7 Greenwich, Ct. (ALS)
Hoffman, Gertrude Wesselhoeft 1946 May 30 Hollywood, Calif. (ALS) 1946 May 31 Hollywood, Calif. (ALS)
Hollenbeck, Don 1946 Jun 3 New York (TLS) 1946 Jun 7 New York (TLS)
Holmes, Alice Marion 1946 Apr 10 Brookline, Mass. (ALS)
Holmes, John Haynes 1946 Mar 19 New York (TLS) 1946 Mar 22 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 8 New York (TLS) 1946 ca. May New York (ALS) 1946 May 28 New York (TLS)
Holt (Henry)& Co., Inc. 1947 Mar 7 New York (TLS, by Mary Willman) 1947 Mar 31 New York (TLS, by Mary Willman)
Howard, Elizabeth 1946 Jul 5 Washington (ALS)
Howe, Mark Antony DeWolfe 1913 Oct 6 Boston (ALS)
Hull, Cordell 1946 Apr 9 Washington (TLS)
Hunter, Allan A. 1946 Apr? Los Angeles (ACS) 1946 May? Los Angeles (TLS)
Hutchins, Robert M. 1946 Jul 8 Chicago (secretarial)
Hutchinson, Paul 1944 Nov 8 Chicago (TLS)
James, Ada E. 1946 May 1 Buffalo, N.Y. (TLS) 1946 May 17 Buffalo, N.Y. (TLS)
Jessup, Philip C. 1934 Feb 8 Washington D.C. (TLS)
Jones, Rufus M. 1946 Mar 19 Haverford, Pa. (TLS) 1946 Apr 16 Haverford, Pa. (TLS)
Kaltenborn, H.V. 1946 Mar 14 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 10 New York (TLS)
Kennedy, Charles Rann 1946 Apr 5 Los Angeles (TLS)
King, Delcevare 1946 May 1 Quincy, Mass. (TLS, to the signers of the Rollins College Appeal) 1946 May 13 Quincy, Mass. (TLS)
Kingdon, Frank 1946 Mar 20 n.p. (TLS)
Knox, Frank 1936 Jun 18 Chicago (TLS)
Lamont, Thomas William 1933 Oct 25 New York (TLS) 1933 Nov 20 New York (TLS) 1934 Jan 23 New York (TLS) 1934 Feb 10 New York (TLS) 1935 May 10 New York (TLS) 1936 Mar 19 New York (TLS) 1947 Aug 20 New York (secretarial)
Lasky, Jesse L. 1946 Apr 26 Hollywood, Calif. (TLS)
Laughlin, Nancy Bartlett 1946 Jun 25 New York, NY Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (ALS) 1946 Jul 15 Southwest Harbor, Me. (ALS)
Lawrence, David 1946 Mar 22 Washington (TLS)
Ledoux, Louis V. 1935 Jun 24 New York (TLS, to Mrs. Laura E. Richards)
Lemmon, Virginia 1946 Mar 14 New York (ALS) 1946 Mar 15 New York (ALS, to "Dear Lady") 1946 Mar 22 New York (ALS, to Dorothy) 1946 Apr 23 New York (ALS) 1946 Apr 26 New York (ALS) 1946 Jun 12 New York (ALS, to Dorothy & "H.H.")
Lenel, Edith G.H. 1945 May 16 Washington (ALS) 1945 May 24 Washington (ALS) 1945 May 27 Washington (ALS) 1945 May 28 Washington (ALS) 1945 May 31 Washington (ALS) 1945 Jun 4 Washington (ALS) 1945 Jun 5 Washington (ALS) 1945 Jun 21 Washington (ALS, enclosed is a plan of the Schweitzer house at Koenigsfeld) 1945 Jul 6 Washington (ALS) 1945 Jul 23 Washington (ALS) 1945 Aug 27 Washington (ALS) 1945 Nov 1 Washington (ALS) 1946 May 29 Washington (ALS) 1946 Jun 11 Washington (ALS) 1946 Sep 8 Washington (postcard)
Lie, Jonas 1936 Apr 6 New York (TLS)
Lippmann, Walter 1946 Mar 21 Washington (secretarial)
Loeb, William ALS 1934 Mar 10 Oyster Bay, NY
London, Jack (with envelope) ALS 1905 Dec 18 Newton, Mass.
Loveman, Amy 1946 Apr 2 New York Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (TLS) 1946 Jun 24 New York (TLS)
Luce, Henry R. 1946 May 20 New York (secretarial)
Luton, George R. 1946 May 14 Santa Barbara, Calif. (ALS)
McCormick, Anne O'Hare 1946 Apr 25 New York (TLS) 1946 May 9 New York (TLS) 1946 Aug 6 New York (postcard)
McCoy, Frank Ross 1936 Jun 3 Governors Island, NY (TLS)
MacDowell, Marian Griswold Nevins (Mrs. Edward) 1936 Jun 30 Peterborough, N.H. (ALS) 1936 Aug 4 Peterborough, N.H. (ALS) 1936 Sep 14 New York (ALS) no date Peterborough, N.H. (ALS)
McKay, Paul L. 1946 Mar 21 New York (TLS)
MacKaye, Percy 1907 Feb 3 Corinth, N.H. (ALS) 1907 Mar 8 Corinth, N.H. (ALS) 1907 Mar 10 Corinth, N.H. (ALS) 1907 Apr 6 Corinth, N.H. (ALS) 1907 May 21 Corinth, N.H. (postcard) 1912 Sep 4 Corinth, N.H. (ALS) 1913 Apr 13 Cambridge (ACS)
MacMillan Company 1945 Apr 23 New York (TLS, by Ellen F. Shippen) 1947 Feb 13 New York (TLS, by Ellen F. Shippen) 1947 Mar 13 New York (TLS, by Mary Lyon) 1947 Mar 31 New York (TLS, by Mary Lyon) 1947 Apr 2 New York (TLS, by Ellen F. Shippen) 1947 Apr 11 New York (TLS, by Ellen F. Shippen) 1961 Dec 13 New York (TLS, by Virginia H. Patterson)
Magee, John G. 1946 Apr 15 New Haven, Ct. (TLS)
Magnin, Edgar F. 1946 Mar 22 Los Angeles (TLS)
Mallery, Otto T. 1946 May 19 Philadelphia (ALS)
Manning, Timothy TLS 1946 Mar 11 Los Angeles
Manning, William Thomas 1946 Mar 23 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 11 New York (TLS)
Marburg, Gertrude 1946 Jun 3 Upper Montclair, N.J. Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (ALS) 1946 Jul 1 Upper Montclair, N.J. (ALS)
Martin, Emmy 1945 Sep 7 Gunsbach, France (ALS) 1945 Nov 18 Gunsbach, France (ALS)
Maurer, Herryman 1947 Oct 6 Chappaqua, N.Y. (TLS)
Meiner, Richard 1955 Oct 5 Hamburg (TLS, to Otto v. Czernicki)
Merrill, Edith 1946 Apr 7 n.p. (ALS)
Mettenet, Jeanne 1945 May ? n.p. (TLS)
Moore, John G. 1946 Jul 12 Hollywood, Calif. (TLS)
Moore, Merrill 1936 Feb 17 Boston (TLS)
Morgan, Angela 1946 May 7 Brattleboro, Vt. (TLS)
Morgan, Daisy A. 1946 May 22 Beverly Hills, Calif. (ALS)
Morrison, Charles Clayton 1946 Jun 7 Chicago (TLS)
Moseley, J.R. 1946 Apr 19 Macon, Ga. (TLS)
Muelder, Walter G. 1944 Oct 2 n.p. (TLS) 1947 Apr 3 Boston (TLS)
Mumford, Lewis 1946 Apr 11 Hanover, N.H. (ALS) 1946 Apr 17 Hanover, N.H. (telegram)
Neilson, William Allan 1906 Sep 30 n.p. (ALS)
Niebuhr, Reinhold 1946 Mar 15 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 10 New York (TLS)
Nies-Berger, Edouard 1945 Mar 18 New York (TLS)
Nixon, Justin Wroe 1946 Mar 26 Rochester, NY (ALS) 1946 Apr 12 n.p. (ANS) 1946 Jul 22 Rochester, NY (ALS)
Oakley, R. Lawrence 1947 Oct 27 New York (TLS)
O'Byrne, E.M. 1946 Jun 12 New York (TLS)
O'Laughlin, John Callan 1946 Mar 20 Washington (secretarial)
Oppenheimer, J. Robert 1946 Apr 12 n.p. (ANS)
Osborn, Chase S. 1933 Dec 8 Poulan, Ga. (TLS) 1934 Feb 2 Poulan, Ga. (TLS) 1934 Feb 2 n.p. (ANS)
Outland, George E. 1946 Mar 14 Washington (TLS)
Oxnam, G. Bromley 1946 Apr 5 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 18 New York (TLS)
Parkinson, Geroge H. 1946 Mar 13 Chicago (TLS)
Peabody, Josephine Preston 1913 Jul 1 Fiesole (postcard, to Mrs. Hermann Hagedorn)
Peet, Hubert W. 1945 Jan 12 Letchworth, England (TLS) 1945 Mar 29 Letchworth, England (TLS) 1945 Apr 3 Letchworth, England (TLS) 1945 Jun 22 Letchworth, England (TLS) 1946 Jul 11 London (TLS) 1946 Jul 18 London (TLS) 1946 Jul 19 London (TLS)
Perry, Bliss 1905 Oct 6 Boston (ACS) 1905 Oct 13 Boston (ALS)
Pettus, John DeForest 1946 Mar 26 Santa Barbara, Calif. (ALS)
Pierson, Medora Belle 1946 Jul 27 Inglewood, Calif. (TLS, to Mrs. Hagedorn)
Pinchot, Gifford 1946 Apr 5 Washington (TLS)
Poling, Daniel A. 1946 Mar 26 Philadelphia (TLS)
Price, Lucien 1905 Sep 8 Kent, Ohio (ALS)
Ralph, Robbins 1946 Jul 9 Northampton, Mass. (TLS, to Mrs. Walter Lemmon)
Ray, Randolph 1946 Mar 22 New York (TLS)
Rector, Beulah 1946 Jul 8 Watertown, NY (TLS)
Regester, John D. 1944 Oct 17 Tacoma, Wash. (TLS)
Reid, Helen Rogers 1957 Oct 28 New York (TLS)
Reiland, Karl 1944 Dec 27 Lindale, Ga. (ALS) 1944 Dec 27 Lindale, Ga. (ALS) 1945 Jan 18 Lindale, Ga. (ALS)
Riach, Alice 1946 May 5 St. Helena, Calif. (TLS)
Richard, Christian 1946 Mar 11 Los Angeles (TLS)
Richards, Laura Elizabeth 1936 Aug 21 Georgetown (ALS)
Rittenhouse, Jessie B. 1913 Mar 13 New York (postcard) 1946 May 28 n.p. (ALS)
Roback, A.A. 1944 Nov 20 Cambridge (ALS) 1945 Jun 26 n.p. (ALS)
Robbins, [ ] 1946 --- -- Ridgewood, N.J. (ALS)
Robbins, Louise 1946 --- -- Cambridge (ALS)
Robins, Raymond 1933 Nov 3 New York (TLS) 1946 Mar 19 Brooksville, Fla. (TLS)
Roosevelt, Edith K. no year Feb 22 Oyster Bay, N.Y. (ALS) 1946 Apr 27 Sagamore Hill (ALS)
Roosevelt, Eleanor 1946 Mar 26 New York (secretarial)
Roosevelt, Nicholas 1946 Apr 24 New York (TLS)
Rosenstock-Huessy, Eugen no date Hanover, N.H. (ALS)
Rowny, J.F. 1946 Mar 31 Santa Barbara, Calif. (TLS)
Russak, M. Sperry 1946 Jun 9 Washington (TLS)
Ryan, Kathryn White 1936 Mar 30 [New York] (TLS) 1936 May 7 Sutton, N.H. (ALS)
Sayre, Nevin 1946 Mar 20 New York (secretarial)
Schenman, Harry 1946 Apr 22 New York Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (TLS)
Schweitzer, Albert Copies of 5 letters, 1944-45, to Hermann Hagedorn are in the Albert Schweitzer research file, box 2.] Copies of 14 letters, 1920-36 (mostly photostats, no originals), to Edith Lenel are in the Albert Schweitzer research file, box 3.] Copies of 3 letters, 1943-44, to Everett Skillings are in the Albert Schweitzer research file, box 3.] Excerpts from letters, 1932-38, to Alice Ehlers are in the Albert Schweitzer research file, box 3.]
Schweitzer, Hélène 1945 Jun 17 Lambaréné (TLS) 1946 May 12 Port Gentil (ALS) 1947 Feb 6 Locarno (ALS) 1947 Feb 22 Mannedorf (TLS) Copy of a letter, 30 April 1944, to Everett Skillings is in the Albert Schweitzer research file, box 3]
Scott, Joseph 1946 Mar 15 Los Angeles (TLS)
Shastid, Thomas Hall 1946 Jul 10 Duluth, Minn. (TLS)
Shaw, Albert 1946 Mar 15 Winter Park, Flor. (ALS) 1946 Apr 8 Winter Park, Flor. (telegram) 1946 Apr 8 Winter Park, Flor. (ALS) 1946 Apr 11 Winter Park, Flor. (ALS) 1946 Apr 30 Winter Park, Flor. (ALS)
Shellabarger, Samuel 1936 May 14 Princeton, N.J. (ALS)
Simon, Ruby Marie no date n.p. (ALS)
Simon and Schuster, Inc., publishers 1947 Mar 19 New York (TLS, by Peter Schwed)
Skillings, Everett 1944 Nov 4 Middlebury, Vt. (TLS) 1945 Feb 8 Middlebury, Vt. (TLS)
Sloss, Mrs. M.C. 1946 Apr 10 San Francisco (TLS, only first page located, to Dear Rita)
Smith, H. Alexander 1946 Mar 19 Washington (TLS)
Smith, Howard Caswell 1946 Mar 21 New York (TLS) 1947 Oct 11 Oyster Bay (ALS)
Smith, J. Herbert 1946 Mar 25 Beverely Hills, Calif. (TLS)
Smith, Roy L. 1946 Mar 28 Chicago (TLS)
Sothern, Edward H. 1905 Dec 4 Boston (ALS) no year Nov 26 Boston (ALS) no year Nov 25 New York telegram no date Boston (ALS)
Speyer, Leonora no year Jan 13 [New York] (ALS)
Starr, Nathan C. 1946 Apr 30 Winter Park, Flor. (TLS)
Stauffer, Milton T. 1946 Jun 11 New York Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (TLS)
Stevens, David H. 1936 Mar 3 New York (TLS)
Stevens, Violet B. 1946 Jun 5 n.p. (ALS)
Stevens, William Bertrand 1946 Apr 18 Los Angeles (ALS)
Stimson, Henry Lewis 1946 May 15 Huntington, N.Y. (TLS)
Stimson, Marshall 1946 Apr 3 Los Angeles (TLS)
Swanton, Walter I. 1936 May 6 Washington (TLS) 1936 May 22 Washington (carbon (carries note on Hermann Hagedorn), to Will R. Gay)
Swing, Raymond 1946 Apr 2 Washington (TLS)
T [ ], Charles H. 1946 Jun 12 New York (TLS)
Tatman, Clarice 1946 Jul 5 Greeley, Col. Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (ALS)
Taylor, Glen H. 1946 Mar 18 Washington (TLS)
Thomas, Lowell 1946 Mar 18 New York (TLS) 1946 Apr 8 n.p. (ANS on returned original of HH, to Lowell Thomas)
Tillich, Paul 1944 Oct 21 New York (TLS)
Torrence, Ridgely 1936 Jul 7 Monhegan Island, Me. (ALS) 1936 Jul 14 Monhegan Island, Me. (ALS) 1936 Aug 27 n.p. (ALS) 1946 Jan 22 n.p. (ALS) 1946 Jan 29 n.p. (ALS)
Truman, Harry S. 1946 Apr 15 Washington (secretarial)
Turner, George Chittenden 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Sheldon Cheney) 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Eugene Exman) 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Frank Fagerburg) 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Harry Emerson Fosdick) 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Aldous Huxley) 1946 Mar 16 Los Angeles (carbon, to Stephen S. Wise)
Tyrrell, Frank G. 1946 Mar 13 Los Angeles (TLS) 1946 Mar 30 Los Angeles (TLS) 1946 Apr 12 Los Angeles (ALS) 1946 Apr 28 Los Angeles (TLS) 1946 May 7 Los Angeles (TLS)
U.S. Post Office Department 1944 Oct 10 Washington (TLS, by Smith W. Purdum)
Vanamee, Grace D. 1936 Mar 17 New York (TLS)
VanDyke, Henry 1905 Dec 29 Princeton, N.J. (ALS)
VanEck, J.C. 1946 Apr 2 Santa Barbara, Calif. (TLS)
vonWindegger, F.R. 1946 Jun 26 St. Louis Pacific Coast Publishing Co. (TLS) 1946 Jul 10 St. Louis (TLS)
Voorhis, Jerry 1946 Mar 25 Washington (TLS)
W-----, Alice H. 1946 Jun 24 New York (TLS, to Gertrude)
?Walgawood, Mrs. Charles W. 1946 Apr 11 Los Angeles (TLS)
Wallace, Henry A. 1946 Apr 9 Washington (TLS)
Walsh, Richard J. 1945 Jun 22 New York (TLS)
Wendell, Barrett 1907 Apr 25 n.p. (ALS) 1913 Jun 11 Cambridge (ALS)
West, Edward 1946 Mar 18 New York (TLS)
Wetmore, Edith 1946 Apr 17 New port, R.I. (ALS, to Mrs. Lemmon) 1946 Jun 3 [New York] (TLS)
Wetmore, Maude K. 1946 Apr 26 [New York] (ALS)
Wolvekamp, Bert 1946 Jun 2 Haarlem (TLS)
Young, Robert R. 1947 Sep 23 Cleveland (TLS)
Zeitlin, Joseph 1946 Mar 18 New York (TLS)
-----, Adele 1946 Apr 30 Los Angeles (ALS)
-----, Ed no date, no place (ALS)
-----, Edward 1946 Apr 24 Cambridge, Mass. (ALS)
-----, Harold 1946 May 22 New York Weyman Huckabee (TLS)
-----, Josh 1946 Apr 26 New York (ALS)
-----, Rosalind 1946 Apr 12 Gardiner, Me. (ALS)
-----, Stephen 1946 May 15 London (TLS)
-----, ----- 1936 Feb 10 Brookline, Mass. (TLS)
-----, ----- 1945 Dec 4 On board the Queen Mary (ALS)
-----, ----- 1946 Mar 14 New York (TLS)
-----, ----- 1946 Apr 4 Pasadena, Calif. (ALS)
-----, ----- 1946 Apr 10 New York (TLS)